[
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_03a_TalkTo_Grace_ReadyInterviews",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_tavern_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_tavern_talkto"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_04_TalkTo_Zander_FirstMeet",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkTo_FirstMeet_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkTo_FirstMeet_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_04_TalkTo_Eynon_HelpSalve",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkToEynon_HelpSalve_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkToEynon_HelpSalve_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Granny_Zander",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_Zander_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_Zander_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Marty",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Marty_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Marty_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Amis",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Amis_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Amis_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Dicun_Investigate",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_Investigate_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_Investigate_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Dicun_CaughtStealing",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_CaughtStealing_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_CaughtStealing_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Granny_ZanderCanJoin",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_ZanderCanJoin_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_ZanderCanJoin_next"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CanJoin",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CanJoin_prompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CanJoin_next",
		"ProvidedTopics": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest"
	},
	{
		"ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest_topicprompt",
		"NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest_cue",
		"RequiredAchievement": "!95_s01_05_DicunGetsAwayTimeline"
	}
]